[
  {
    "Front": "γαµέω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: gifter mig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γάµος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: bryllup"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γάρ",
    "Back": " konj.: thi, for"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γελάω",
    "Back": " vb.: ler"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γελοῖος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: latterlig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γέλως",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: latter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γένεσις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: tilblivelse"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γένος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: slægt, art"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γέρων",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: gammel person"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γεύοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: smager"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γῆ",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: land"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γίγνοµαι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: bliver"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γιγνώσκω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: erkender, lærer at"
  },
  {
    "Front": "kende"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γλυκύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: sød"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γλῶττα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: tunge, sprog"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γνώµη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: mening"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γονεύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: fader, (plur.) forældre"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γράφω",
    "Back": " vb.: skriver"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γυµνός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: nøgen"
  },
  {
    "Front": "γυνή",
    "Back": " sb. ureg.: kvinde"
  }
]